Good girl, Ruby. Good girl. Let's say you're like, I got to buy something today. Don't call
me mans. You don't know me. That's, that is only for family. So let's say you're like,
I got to buy today. Um, I have no choice. At least try to spend cash. At least try to spend cash.
Because the other part of this is freezing the debt-based economy and these apps like
PayPal, as well as these credit cards. Right? So that's why, that's why when people are like,
um, you know, I have no choice. Um, or what about black businesses? First of all,
let me just tell you something. Just because a business is owned by black people does not mean
they are not absolutely complete capitalists that are consistently supporting the nonsense of this
nation. Just because they black don't mean they ain't white. I painted it. Um, nobody tell me
nothing. I love it. And that's just what it is. I'm very proud of this piece. That was the first
painting I did in, yeah. Anyhow, I think I'm going to put another piece right there. So I say all that
to say that like, I really, yes, let's say all that to say, why did I come up here when I know I
have a hammer downstairs? Listen, I got a weapon in every part of my house. You hear me? Ain't nobody
surprising me. Nope. Nobody running up on me in my house. There's, there's, there's a weapon in every
turn. For all my single women, you better keep a weapon everywhere. So yeah, like it's, it's not,
it's not that you can't change. It's just that you haven't really been challenged to. And that's the
thing is that we haven't really been challenged to. And so we keep up these old habits and we act like
we act like we can't figure something else out. When that's literally all humans do. Y'all,
Haymarket Books sent me a box of books. Like humans stay adapting. Oh, damn. So if you're not
gonna, so if you're gonna, if you have to spend today, you're like, oh my God, Amanda, please try,
at least try to spend cash. So my first grade teacher and her daughter, who's my really good
friend are coming over today. And let me just tell y'all the last time my first grade teacher
came to my house, she immediately started cleaning. So I feel so much pressure. I feel so much pressure.
And if y'all are asking about bookshelves, let me just tell you about these Ikea bookshelves.
I have had the same Ikea bookshelves since 2018. Yes. I have had the same Ikea bookshelves
since 2018. They're white. And I think people really forget that my credits number. I've had
the same Ikea bookshelves since 2018. And I keep fixing them. And, um, TNA, Miss Butta,
some clutter house equals equates to a cluttered mind. Where do people come up with this type
of shit? It's, my shit ain't cluttered. It's where it's supposed to be. This is going to be
my library. It just hasn't been put up on the shelves. As you can see, my house ain't cluttered.
Everything is, is in its right place. Everything in its right place.
So this is a, an Ikea bookshelf that I'm in the process of restoring to strengthen it again.
Hi, Mando. And so I had to get this clamp thing so I could hold it together so that I could do what
I need to do. Um, so yeah, I just, I just really am again, just trying to remind folks that if you're
going to spend today, only spend on a necessity. Like I saw somebody in here say that they need a
3D printer for school and it is least expensive today. And I am not going to refute that. That
sounds like an actual fact. So like, do what you got to do, you know, do what you got to do,
but also know that, um, that you don't got to OD. Well, let me block this person real quick.
Yes. My first and second grade teacher. Uh, I am on a group chat with both my first and second grade
teacher. Teachers. Or we could buy shit and return it. Yup. Like they did at Home Depot. That was lit.
That was lit. And it's right. So I want to let everybody know that I will be in DC. Apparently
the tickets in DC are sold out, which I can't say that I actually fully believe. So I'm going to have
to confirm that today. Um, my mom be doing way too much. Um, but I will also, I will be in Houston on
the, I'll be in Baltimore on the 3rd of December. And then I'll be in Houston on December 10th,
New Orleans, December 11th, Atlanta, December 13th and tattoo December 15th. Nope. December 14th.
Yes, that is my odds. The God, the Egyptian goddess of truth and justice, which y'all know is what I'm
all the F about. And it's right. So some of people are asking about cities like Minneapolis. And so
here's the thing, this book tour is completely funded by me. Like, it's not like I'm, you know,
it's not like, so there's book, there's bookstores who are like, well, you know, we, you have to pay
us a percentage, you know, or else it's like pointless for us to do a book, um, signing with
you because we're not getting anything out of it. And you know, they reserve the right to say that.
Okay. He's not the biggest Zio, but he is an idiot. He's not like, you can't say that Tom York is the
biggest Zio when there are people out here, like, I don't know when there are people out here that
are bigger Zios. However, he is a ridiculous person. Um, any who, what I was going to say is that
I just feel like there's, what was I going to, what was I going to say? I don't even remember what I
was talking about. So I am, I am the one paying for my tour. My book tour is spent by me. So like
when you have a book that is with a product, with a publishing company, they are the ones who end up
covering the cost of your book tour typically. However, um, you know, I don't have a publishing
company and you know, ultimately I am paying for this book tour with the sales that are made from
the book. So I can't go to cities yet where I don't know that I have a following because it ends
up being, um, too much of like a financial risk. I just left Detroit. Um, so places like Minneapolis,
Phoenix, Portland, um, Boston, these are places. I know there are people that love my work and that,
that want to link with me. I know they're there and I want to get there. However, first off,
well, I'll be in Dallas on the 14th, but first off, I have to go to places where I know that I
can have some financial support, um, in order to continue the work I'm doing. And I really want
to get into the practice of supporting myself really mainly through books. That's really what I
want to do. Like, I want to have you guys be able to buy pins and, you know, things like this are so
fun. And they're also like, my work is also very grounded in real things. However, I really want
to be able to have more time in my life to consistently be writing and, um, Oh, good.
Talia, that's actually really, thank you for telling me that I'm going to reach out to you
because I'm working on that, um, to do more writing and creating and art. And so like, I'm really
working on like setting up my life to do that. Um, I want to come to Jackson, Mississippi too,
and I'm working on coming to Birmingham. So if I go to Birmingham, Alabama, um, when I go to
Birmingham, Alabama, I plan to come to Mississippi next. Yes. I'm working on an audio book. I'm actually
recording it in two weeks and I'll be putting it out in February. Uh, I'm working on being in Philly
in January or February. The best. There's some of y'all on here who it's like, I feel like God sent
you specifically to me to just keep me lifted. Talia is one of them. And it's right. So I found all of
my, um, I found all of my workbooks and, and reading materials from my graduate program.
So I'm about to, I'm about to get into all of that. I, I put together, I put together and shipped
70 orders last night and I am now up to date. So my store, I'm about to close my store.
I'm closing my store till December 5th. And I know that's going to hurt my sales. Oh, well,
I'm closing my store till December 5th so that I don't have any orders to, to, to put together.
And, um, cause when I had that hanging over my head, it's like an app draining my battery.
So I, I closed my store. I closed my store. Jennifer, Jennifer, um, Jennifer Lewis did a song
saying we not shopping till December 5th. And I said, all right. So I closed my store till December 5th
and that's just how it's going to be. No, no black owned shopping. We, black people are not,
are not exempt from being a part of continue. We be serving the commercial GDP of this country.
No, don't buy shit from nobody. Unless it's a necessity.
Every time that you use your credit card, every time that you use PayPal, every time you use the shop
app, you are keeping all of this going, right? Like you're, you're, you're contributing. So even if
you say, well, but I'm buying black. Yeah, but they're still getting a cut. They're still getting
a cut. They're not stupid. So the only version of buying black has to be cash.
And there's only, there's no version of cash that's digital. There's no version of cash that's
digital. Okay. Thank you. Teddy's mommy. Like we have to like, get into the practice of this.
We have to get into the practice of it. And the only way to get into the practice of it is to make
yourself not exempt. Mando. No, it's too cold. And you know what? Like Talia said right here,
consumerism. Like the religion in this country, this is not a Jesus loving country or any of that.
This is a money loving country, a money spending country. That is our religion. Shopping. Shopping
is the American religion. I say that as an avid shopper and having to actually curb my shopping habit.
So here's some books that I'm trying to get into. Okay. We got the history of pen African
revolt by CLR James. I bought, I bought CLR James, his entire, um, his, his entire catalog. CLR James
is a Trinidadian black intellectual. Okay. He died in 1989. This is, um, the selected writings
of CLR James. Uh, this is every cook can govern. This is about socialism. This is about socialism,
state capitalism and world revolution. Okay. Uh, Nekruma and the Ghana revolution.
Because I can hear Mando meowing and he be, he be meowing trying to tell me like, Hey,
like let me out. And it's like, no, I'm not letting you out. Cut it out. This is the lost art of reading
nature signs. Use outdoor clues to find your way, predict the weather, locate water, track animals
and other forgotten skills. You missed the book titles. I mean, it's just CLR James. So look up CLR
James. I make reading lists all the time, Talia. And then I get tired of it. I really just need to
take a month off. I really need to take a month off to just think. I ain't even gonna lie to you.
I ain't even gonna hold you. I really need to take a month for real, uh, for real month to just
think. Because I never do. I never do. But that's really what I, I really want to do that. I was,
I was just in Grenada trying to find a place so I could stay there for three months and I couldn't
find a place. Oh yeah. Talia, we have a book club on, on Patreon now, but this is a great example.
So I bought this thing called Remarkable and I just thought I was gonna live by this thing.
I had never used it and it was not cheap and I, I never used it. This is by a Grenadian artist
and he's autistic. And when you go in the shops that sell his work, we, it's, it's always funny
because you know what kind of paint somebody donated to him because everything will be that color.
So it's like, oh, somebody hit him up with some red paint. All we got is red stuff right now. Oh,
he came up on some blue paint. Anything blue. No, I hope, I hope that at some point I can just go be
in Grenada and I can sell my art in Grenada and write my books and go and inspire folks and teach
whenever needed. And, um, I hope that one day my home can be, uh, a sanctuary of sorts for, um,
writers and, um, programs and things like that. Like that's what I really want one day. I want one day
that this home I'm living in right here is a place where literally like it's a organization
for black teens and they are able to come here and be a part of political education classes.
They're able to come here and take art class, be a part of art classes. They're able to come here
and, um, organize, et cetera. But now Instagram is doing its thing where it turns off my comments.
So I'm going to go, let's stay the course. Y'all don't spend today.
Ba-dum-bum!